# MIKAILA IVERY

#### FRONTEND

## **PROFILE INFO**

Solution-driven individual who collaborates well in teams. Exceptional communication skills. Technically proficient with more than 1 year of frontend development experience. Skilled in using web technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React Js, and more.

## **CONTACT INFO**



#### **Phone**

Request via Email



#### **Email**

iverymikaila@gmail.com



## Location

Brooklyn, New York



#### **Portfolio**

mikailaivery.com

## MY SKILLS

React is

Web Design

HTML5 /CSS3

Javascript

Bootstrap

Responsive Design

React Native

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Frontend Developer** Freelance / Self Employed

**2022 - PRESENT** 

- Developed and designed custom HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Shopify clients, resulting in improved website functionality and customer satisfaction.
- Maintained quality website functionality through ongoing updates and troubleshooting.
- Created visually appealing prototypes on Figma or Canva that accurately reflected client needs and preferences.

#### Tutor

2022-2023

#### **Grade Potential Tutoring**

- Helping students learn and understand new concepts and complete assignments
- Tutoring subjects: Basic Web Development, K-12 Math/English Curriculum

## Cashier **Target**

2017-2018

 Processing/ receiving payments, and issuing receipts to customers.

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

# **AAS in Advertising Marketing**

**Communications** 

2019 - 2021

## **Fashion Institute of Technology**

- · National Society of Leadership and Success nominee/member
- Overall GPA: 3.4; A in Statistical Analysis Course

**Highschool Diploma Midwood High School** 

2015 - 2019

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

## **SheCodes Workshops**

2021 - 2022

Advanced React Development

Certificate ID:

d612b3f586475714368519fef0c7cb09 9973-77d28e46589f

#### **Noble Desktop**

2022

HTML Email Bootcamp

Certificate ID:5e75641e-8b03-44ae